Welcome to the Weather App!

This application provides weather information sourced from two providers: OpenWeatherMap 
and Open-Meteo. To access weather data, you will need to register with OpenWeatherMap and 
acquire a personal API key. 

Here's how to get started:
1. Register at OpenWeatherMap: Sign up on the OpenWeatherMap website to create an 
account. For the purpose of this app a free subscription is enough.
2. Retrieve Your API Key: After registering, log in to your OpenWeatherMap account and 
navigate to your profile. Click on "My API keys" to generate a personal API key. Copy this 
key as you'll need to paste it into the designated line in the code (indicated as api_key). 

With your API key ready, you're all set to use the Weather App:
1. Run the Code: Execute the provided code. A popup window will appear.
2. Enter Location: In the popup window, input the desired city and its corresponding country code. 
3. Select Language: Choose the language for the app interface. You can choose between English, Czech and Slovak.
4. Choose Weather Display: The app offers three distinct buttons:
	• What’s the weather?: This button provides essential weather details such as temperature, wind speed, and precipitation.
	• More information: Select this button for more comprehensive weather information.
	• 7-Day Forecast: The final button generates a chart displaying a 7-day temperature forecast.

By following these steps, you'll be able to utilize the Weather App effectively and access the 
weather information you need.

For seamless execution of the code, please keep both the Python code file and the folder 
containing visual icons in the same directory. Further, please, ensure that you have the following 
packages installed: requests, Pillow, numpy, and matplotlib. To do that first install 'pip' (usually 
comes installed with Python versions 3.4 and above), open a terminal or command prompt and 
then execute the following commands: 

pip install requests 

pip install pillow

pip install numpy

pip install matplotlib


